The Capricorn's mountain throne, with Aquarius dreams that chill to the bone.
Mercury speaks with authorities fire, while Venus nap to lift souls ever higher.
Stormborn architect of impossible realm.
Where shadows integrate and healing overwhelms, they call you dangerous, for speaking what's true
And hearts find their healing in electric profit, lightning in your veins
Dancing with darkness, breaking all the chains, they shame what you carry
They fear what you see, but you're the bridge builder, setting spirits free
Upon walking mids, we're on and right
The outcasts find you the wound to come home
You're never alone
Within the Scorpio power run
While Matangie's wisdom has never once failed
They hunt what you treasure
They mock what you need
But your sacred rebellion
Plants freedom see
Reading us most in cards and ends
Nothing is ever quite what it seems
Persecuted prophet with love in your heart
Torn by their hatred, yet playing you
Dancing with bliss, breaking all the chains
They shame what you carry, they fear what you see
But you're the rich builder set in spirits free
Me between all mind you
You're never as your shell hard as you
Oh, here's a Phantom video. Am I in it?
He deserves the, what?
Who's a phantom video? Oh, big clubs. Why don't you leave leave? Where is the phantom video? I don't know
Is the phantom the opera?
There's a phantom video. Hold on. I like phantom videos. There's a phantom. That's it right here. I found it
phantom
Do I dream again?
Oh, no, I really don't want to die.
Is that it?
Is that a dance from video?
I'm not sure.
Oh, it was you?
Oh, OK.
It was me, it was me.
My microphone was on the floor.
I'm sorry, it was me.
It was my fault.
Is that Rudy?
Rudy's in the house?
It's OK.
My fault.
Hi, Rudy.
What are you doing?
You're over here licking yourself on our, or sorry,
When I was sleeping over on the other side, what are you doing? You've been sleeping with me all morning
I saw you you get in under the covers. What's wrong with you?
Mmm, I don't know. I might walk to the store
But if I do I can't bring anybody up because I'll be on my phone. I can't like figure out how to
Hold I don't know. You're bored
Most hated. Well, what is like the who's the phantom video?
You're bored, how about watching about my genealogy?
Wouldn't that be interesting?
Let's see how important I am.
Entertain you, okay.
I have a slideshow actually,
so I'll just talk you through it.
I won't play the video, but this could be, you know.
Think you'll like this, so let me see my,
let me grab this PDF file.
You're typing the wrong tab, it's okay.
Let me see, I haven't, okay, here we go.
Here's the, let me see if it works.
Wait, wait, wait, is there one left?
I don't want to see.
Oh my God.
It's actually really interesting.
What I did was, I ran like,
I mean, I have like these extra results.
They were talking about the Carmelo stabbing.
Like who, but it was that white guy that did it, wasn't it?
Or no, no, it wasn't.
I mean, so that did it, but that like got stabbed
and it was like the black Carmelo did it.
I don't know.
This is called the illuminated lineage.
This is my, oops, sorry, my curated archeological.
History a big screen the Carmelo stabbing. I mean, it's like pretty obvious. I mean if you watch
Okay
This has my name on it and stuff. So you can tell it's real. Okay. Hold on
So there's basically where I'm from right there. It's a deeply rooted genetic signature or anchored in British Germanic
interface. I have all this R1B DNA 72% and I have 23% H1H3 DNA. I think the R1B is
paternal lineage. My closest living populations are the wealthy English and
the West Germans. Okay, let's see what else it says. Oh shoot. Okay, three
distinct civilizations form the foundational triad of my ancestry. The
The Franks, which are the Germanic French and the Dobuni, which were the Celtic. Okay. This is a very short presentation by the way
Defining era for the Celtic
Well, it says, you know, there's like three also words that come up which is pagan
Viking and
Druid
Okay, so I guess those would be like the kind of a cultic
sides of each of these civilizations
He tribes Dobuni, Britons, Cantiachi, and Cattu-Villiani,
and Germanic migration, Alemani, Franks, Saxons, Visigoths.
The Celtics were these indigenous populations before
during the Roman contact, massive population movements
of the Germans following the collapse of the Western Roman Empire.
Interesting.
Okay, my lineage tracks across five distinct
epics of European history, the Bronze Age.
So I have deep pre-Celtic foundations with the bell beaker and rado vesike
Iron if you know any of these like or information about any of these civilizations, you know, let me know too
I'm always like learning learning more iron age the dominant Celtic era indigenous Britons
Then there's a Germanic influx during the Roman collapse
Then we have some Norse settlement out of Britain and Northern France DNA and continue
Northern European heritage and trade connections. Okay, that's my background.
There's a direct link to the aristocratic class of the early Celtic world because I am very closely
and Magdalene Berg, Germany.
Okay, maybe she was Mary Magdalene.
I don't know, but it's a little bit early, I guess,
but maybe they have the timing off a little bit.
Curator's note, or here's note,
the match pieces mean the top 99% of all platform users
recovered from the Hallstop period in Southwestern Germany.
This individual belonged to the highest aristocratic class
of the early Iron Age Celtic world.
Okay, that's pretty cool. So maybe I am related to fairies and stuff like that. I'm not sure, you know
aliens fairies
Something interesting was happening
I'm in the elite, right?
The platform users are all the people on this website called my true ancestry. I'm in the top percentage
Also related to an elite Iron Age warrior
in a Rod Dovesi Bohemia
250 BC and it's a male and I'm
In the top 99% related to him an elite warrior's burial representing
Celtic Latene culture the group dominated central Europe's militarily and culturally prior to the widespread Germanic
migrations, okay
So the collapse of the Roman Empire catalyzed my German migration that shaped my modern DNA
And you can see it's just going all around Europe from here, right?
Down to Spain a little bit or portrait. Yes, it's Spain right there. But yeah, right? I've been I've actually been to Spain
I've been to the Czech Republic which is right here
I believe and I've been to Amsterdam which is like right here and then there's Germany up here
So I've been all over this place is a coastal defender from the ancestral homelands of the Anglo-Saxons
So I'm in the top 95% related to the Saxon coast defender. Okay, also
Copperage pioneer 99 percent percentile and 96 percentile for this bell beaker culture. Okay
So I'm a synthesis of the Celtic elite the German migratures the Norse
Expansions of the Viking that the Druids the Pagans and the Vikings, right?
And that turns to my modern living relatives and I have had witches and all kinds of things in my background
But that's it. I mean, that's a short presentation. I hope you find that
Interested so tell me the story of the Carmelo Anthony. Oh, it's everyone left that was just too boring for anybody
I mean it was like 10 slides. It was like not even like
I was just saying, you know, I'm pretty special, but it's okay. Yeah, so tell me about the Carmelo Anthony thing
I mean, I mean, it's like I was thinking it was that Carmelo Anthony basketball player. I was like, oh no
So was so a phantom did it phantom killed him. I mean, what's going on? I mean, there's a video of phantom
It's he getting me released from prison. Is he you know, I think it's has all the all the workings of a Psyop
because they do these psyops to upset but it's very controversial when I talk
about it but we can see on the view I guess there was like a little clip about
it now there's Carmelo Anthony looks like bad news you know I don't know what
happened after he started playing for like the Denver Nuggets but it looks
like he's gone downhill you know he's okay we'll check it out here
What happened on the view today? Do you think Joy Behar got to the bottom of things?
Who's sunny?
Hauston is a sunny Hauston a woman on the view
Never heard of her sunny hosting her name is sunny hosting and she's a host
It's pretty good. Okay. Here we go. There's the view
Happen with a Jeff Met calf like you know, isn't a calf like a cow and they kind of think humans are cattle, right?
I don't know. These are just ideas. What are we watching dancing?
Where's the volume and stuff?
Play clip for you, which I'm not going to have sunny Houston on the view saying I don't understand
How this couldn't possibly be self-defense?
So what is your judgment of all these people in the media that have spoken on the case?
Well, they're just like anybody else. They don't know me. They don't know Hunter Austin. They don't know Carmelo
They're looking for their 15 minutes of fame or their click bait or their clicks
They're looking to monetize the death of my son
I really wish they wouldn't speak about it at all, because one, if that woman said that,
she has no idea about the facts of the case, but she wants to spew her public opinion on
a platform that reaches millions of people every day.
Do I have that platform?
No, but today I have a little flat woman to say what I like.
She is completely wrong.
and if they won't take me and call me
and ask me to be able to view with them,
I would gladly fly.
Fly me up there, let me talk to all of you.
Well, I can promise you more people are watching you right now
than watch the view.
That's not what I'm saying.
I don't think so.
What is this, the CNBC or something?
I mean, what, ridiculous.
I can promise you more people are watching you
than the view right now.
Well, I mean, it's like true in a certain way.
Mean like nobody really watches the view, but then nobody watches this shit either. I mean nothing nuts do like me
Okay, so there's a sad story. So the sad story is this guy
You know, there's there's okay. So here's how it's being presented. It's like there's this beautiful like white person, right?
He's like this muscular. He was a football player. He's sitting with his like football. He's blonde. He's like all American
Just like, you know, pop the most popular guy in the school. Okay, and so then there's this
Black guy who he was named after Carmelo Anthony. So, you know, I mean, it's like so we can tell so there are
Sport fans all around right we can tell their sports fans
But in the Carmelo Anthony, and I guess they were an attract team.
It wasn't even a football team.
It was like they'd read track or something and there was a track meet.
Am I wrong guys?
You have to tell me, was it a football game or a track?
You need to like correct me because it's like, I just like, I watched these and
I'm like, Oh my God.
But yeah, there were a track meet or something.
And then there was an argument over like who could sit where.
And I don't know if like they said no black people can sit here or something
like that. I don't know.
It doesn't sound like.
How people would talk nowadays like but then it was like and then then it was like this
So then Carmelo turns into like this is how that's presented in the media
This is how it's like he's like he's presented now as this like angry black guy
That was like me bullied and was just like had his knife and just couldn't take it anymore and just like walked right up
To the guy and stab him in the corner and then like then like wouldn't hug hug the coach and something else
Can someone explain the story after the bathroom movie? I'm gonna explain the story
if I got it wrong, and I'll go into it.
Here, I'll put this, I'll put the info thing on.
We're back, we're back.
Oh my gosh.
So sorry.
Hey, by the way, Minnie Manson,
thank you for the great feedback about the video.
That's no problem, but I'm happy that you liked it, okay?
Yeah, thank you for being on my show last year
and hope to see you again.
And Minnie Manson enjoyed the explainer video I made.
So, here we go, here we go, we're back.
Rise the midnight in a faded green coat Headphones glowin' while the city stays remote
Nobody notices the queen beside the door The goddess of the outcasts walkin' every
floor She laughs through static speakers in a liquor store
Paint the teensin' broken dreams stacked from floor to floor
A janitor hums a melody nobody can place Ancient sounds grit hidein' underneath his base
She's the whisper and the wire The song beneath the noise
I know I wasn't downplaying. I was saying the guy was murdered now. Everyone else is downplaying. They're saying, well, there should have been. Here's the excuses that I don't like that I hear. They say,
First of all, oh, I heard it wasn't on it wasn't I'm gonna get on film
Okay, well that how many murders are on film and this is like a snuff film or something
They very few so it's like you don't need there's other evidence and there's other things on video, right? There's also
Um, I don't like the excuse. Well, there's no black people on the jury
That shouldn't have I mean but that's sadly that sometimes does have things like that to do with like
You know justice, but so does having an all-black jury on this situation could have the same thing if it was like, you know
He was found like, you know completely. Hey Nancy. How are you? Good to see you. Good to see you, Vinette. Thanks for coming today
Yeah, I mean it's like I mean someone brought this story up and I don't really go into like you know
But I do like true crime right right and so I'll talk about it. I mean I have a limited
Thing that I watched about it, right? I watched something about it and I have my own conclusions that I jumped to but it's like, you know
I can't go into like
too much of my own
opinions about it but I mean it's like because it's like I think that the whole
thing is there's like this chessboard in America the chessboard has black and
white pieces and that's like the extremes of like these both sides. I'm not
even racial about it I was saying black and white is like you know on the
chessboard and then but it is used in a certain way it's like because blacks and
whites have kind of like the biggest I would say
Contrast in a certain way. I mean they look the most different they most have the most other most extreme skin size of the skin colors
But it's like but I think that's like the biggest thing is just a skin color, right?
It's like
Well, but there's culture cultural things and like, you know, a lot of other stuff that's happened to right so
I just don't want to sound dumb talking about this kind of stuff, but hi. Hi guys. Yeah, I'm a black cat
I have this color cat and whatever color you are. I love you
See the cats are they're called their furs are different color. It doesn't make them a different kind of
Thing it's like, you know, some people were like, oh, they I mean some people are under the impression that different races are like different species of like
I mean, it's like I think that there's just some genetic variation, but there's not
Like, a difference between people.
Christina's going to live again, but she demoted...
Oh, she's going live again, but she demoted you as a mod.
You wonder why. You can take a guess who and why.
It's ridiculous.
Yeah, I'm sorry, Nancy. Yeah, it's like, you know, she has that.
Well, Christine is just terrible like to me like all I mean, I'll see all she can say is like what she's what she's going to do
Like it's really obvious what she's doing, which is a kind of like dehumanizing or
It's a gang-stalking thing that people do which is like
They'll start associating your name with like terrible things and then it's like then and people will just like like um
Like she treats these things that they're like um like what like?
Pavlovian dogs or something like where it's like because she keeps saying oh
Sanky you you just have shit. You're digging shit in your ass and like just like saying like negative
Associations and like but that's what she says every time I see her and then she comes up and starts screaming it over and over
And over and over again, and so it's like that's all that she has
But basically people know the trick and it's kind of like it doesn't work really, but it can like have an effect on
Some people that will just be like, oh, yeah, he's I don't like him because I just like that
You know that I get a bad like no bad vibe because people are saying oh you fucking
Digg shit through your nail like but it's like it's like it's like these really like
vivid
Negative pictures are trying to present plus they don't even like forget about just like saying those things then they put
They make the AI that we're being to each other, but she ended them. She ended the mod. Yeah
I mean, it's gonna be very passive aggressive.
Well, it's probably because she probably sees you
in here too.
I mean, that might be a reason too.
I mean, it's like they've been attacking people in my chat.
They've been, you know, attacking me.
I mean, it's like, and I haven't really done,
I mean, it's like for what reason?
I don't know, I get called all kinds of things.
I get called a doxxer.
I mean, I doxx myself more than anybody, right?
I've doxxed myself.
I've used a thumbnail.
Of this publicly available picture. Yeah, it's crazy. It's very passive-aggressive. It's very
Almost like, you know, well, so you just just be just be happy or not
You know, you're not hidden there because it's just she sees this will probably just hide you and and
And say you're like a bad person or a pet a predator protector or something. I mean, it's like that's what they do
I mean, that's all there. I don't know if it's like
I don't know why the hate for me came. I think it's like I think it right at this point
It must be just because I'm like, you know, they think I'm like getting
Like ten of their views or something like that
This used to be one of my key financial brat backers now and say key, but there was a night
I got a couple hundred bucks. I'm donated from Christine
And then there's other, you know, there's pretty nice donations.
I will say she's like one of the most notorious clappers that pays for people to get, they
get clapped.
And so, and then it's like, but then it's like, so I guess like if people donate at
one point, then they expect, well, he's not gonna have Crystal Marie on, you know, speculating
Kids. I mean, is that a little bit too much to ask at Christine?
I mean, Christine is so unpredictable.
I mean, it's like, and I wasn't,
if you watch back, which is why I played
that stupid clip so many times, you didn't watch it,
you just, all you heard was, you know, you killed kids.
No, I was saying, no, she, not our Christine,
or that you're thinking of Christine,
you know, Christina Ricci or something like,
I don't know, like a different Christine.
And I didn't even think her real name was Christine,
but then it turns into like, oh,
Now, now when, you know, some kid gets hit by a bicycle and is like, you know, dying,
the parents are going to say, oh, there's Christine, she's just going to kill him.
Can I have a different nurse, please?
I don't quite think that's how it works in the medical industry.
I mean, I don't.
First of all, I don't think that the parents are there choosing like the medical personnel,
you know, in the emergency room and say, oh, no, I saw that I saw that woman's face,
on an obscure, you know...